[{"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 6, "", 8], [6, 5, "", "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 5, 7], [4, 3, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 5, 6, "", ""], [6, "", "", "", 2]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 7, 8], [5, 4, 3]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 6, "", 8, ""], ["", 7, "", "", 4]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 7, 9], [8, 6, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[3, "", "", "", 7], ["", 9, "", "", 6]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 5, 6], [10, 8, 7]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 7, 8, ""], [6, "", "", "", 2]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 9], [5, 4, 3]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 5, "", 7, ""], [6, 5, "", "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 6, 8], [4, 3, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 8, 9], ["", 6, 5, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 7], [7, 4, 3]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[4, 5, "", "", ""], ["", 8, "", "", 5]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 7, 8], [9, 7, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 8, 9], [9, 8, "", "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 7], [7, 6, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", "", 9, 10], [6, "", 4, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 7, 8], [5, 3, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 3, "", "", 6], ["", 8, "", 6, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 4, 5], [9, 7, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[6, 7, "", "", ""], ["", 5, 4, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[8, 9, 10], [6, 3, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 4, "", "", 7], [10, "", 8, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 5, 6], [9, 7, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 3, "", 5, ""], ["", "", 8, 7, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[2, 4, 6], [10, 9, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[4, "", "", 7, ""], ["", "", 7, "", 5]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 8], [9, 8, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 4, "", "", 7], [6, "", "", 3, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 5, 6], [5, 4, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[4, "", "", "", 8], ["", "", 6, 5, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 7], [8, 7, 4]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[2, "", "", "", 6], ["", 5, "", 3, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 4, 5], [6, 4, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[5, "", "", "", 9], [8, "", "", "", 4]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 7, 8], [7, 6, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[3, "", "", "", 7], [8, "", 6, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 5, 6], [7, 5, 4]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 5, "", 7, ""], ["", "", 8, "", 6]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 6, 8], [10, 9, 7]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 5, 6, ""], ["", 5, "", 3, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 4, 7], [6, 4, 2]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 4, "", "", 7], [7, "", "", "", 3]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 5, 6], [6, 5, 4]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[5, "", "", "", 9], [6, "", "", "", 2]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 7, 8], [5, 4, 3]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 6, "", 8], ["", "", 8, 7, ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[4, 5, 7], [10, 9, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[2, "", 4, "", ""], ["", "", "", 5, 4]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[3, 5, 6], [8, 7, 6]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[5, "", 7, "", ""], ["", "", "", 7, 6]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 8, 9], [10, 9, 8]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", 7, 8, "", ""], ["", 8, 7, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[6, 9, 10], [9, 6, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [["", "", 7, 8, ""], ["", 9, "", "", 6]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 9], [10, 8, 7]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}, {"body": [{"title": "填一填（多个输入框）", "stem": "按顺序填数", "content": [[4, "", "", 7, ""], ["", 8, 7, "", ""]], "showType": "s", "animalImg": "animal_tardigvada_right/6f5c724ea90d5e90d33164e874dee461.svg", "type": "number-multiple-input", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [[5, 6, 8], [9, 6, 5]], "knowledges": ["10以内数的排序"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "2", "number": "1-1-10-04"}]